It's not an offside, ref!
Fuck!
-Beto...
-What?
-I want to tell you something.
-Wait till it ends.
No, Cruz Azul will lose.
You know that.
-It's important, man.
-Tell me.
Your breath stinks.
-What?
-That's it. Your breath stinks.
Your breath is rotten,
like you used poop mouthwash.
-Right now?
-Yes. And always. Always.
Your mouth has always smelled
like an abandoned fishery.
You know?
A full bus in the summer.
A morgue with no energy.
-I don't feel anything.
-C'mon! You're used to it.
If your mouth was the groin
of a dead crook,
it would smell better.
Your saliva is like that liquid
that comes from organic trash.
What if I brush my teeth?
Only if you use
turpentine and thinner.
You need professional help,
Beto.
-A dentist?
-No... An exorcist.
Why didn't you tell me
before?
Because every time I try,
I feel like my face will melt!
I can talk facing forward
because I have sinusitis,
but my eyes are burning.
Does everyone know?
I think they don't
in Australia.
We do this because we love you
and want to help you.
-Goal!
-What a goal!
-Celebrate in silence!
-Fuck!
-Fuck off, man!
That's a bad move, man.
-What a goal!
-Fuck!
That's bad, man.